STAŠA STANIŠIĆ

PHP DFVFI OPFR

PERSONAL DETAILS

∴: Senjačka 27, Belgrade
 ∴: stasas@gmail.com
 : +381 63 352 694
 ∴: +381 11 2650 202
 DOB: 16.01.1982
 Gender: Male

Nationality: Serbian, Slovenian

SKILLS

- PHP
- SQL
- HTML
- XML
- MongoDB
- JavaScript
- CSS
- VisualBasic
- PHPUnit testing framework
- Laravel framework
- Git Version Control
- Sublime Text, Eclipse
- DBMS: MySQL, MS SQL Server, MS Access
- Adobe Photoshop
- OS: MS Windows, Debian Linux, Mac OS X

EDUCATION

Fakultet organizacionih nauka 2000 -

Treća beogradska gimnazija 1996 - 2000

LANGUAGES

- English (expert)
- Spanish (advanced)
- French (beginner)

INTERESTS

- Mobile development
- UI/UX development
- Photography
- Travel

PROFILE

A resourceful, competent PHP developer experienced in designing and implementing applications and solutions for a wide range of corporate, public sector and private clients.

Considerable knowledge of web development using PHP programming language with MySQL and MS SQL Server as database management systems. Experienced working within an IT team of six people supporting more than 150 users for various software, therefore producing well formatted, readable and maintainable code and dynamic effective websites. Further, competent working on individual projects due to contract work for a range of clients. Responsible person with a strong focus on creativity and problem solving and always ready for further improvement and learning, hoping to continue building my skills, expanding them to take in a wider scope of environments and languages such as Java and mobile development, on a suitable developer position with an ambitious and exciting company.

EXPERIENCE

MERCEDES-BENZ Srbija i Crna Gora d.o.o., 2006 - 2014 APPLICATION DEVELOPER

• <u>Development and support of Car Sales and Customer Management</u> software

Over 50 users utilized the software, covering all company processes of retail, logistics and wholesale business units. Personally responsible for communicating with business unit representatives about new software functionality as well as programming and implementing the changes and supporting the software users.

- Design, development and support of After Sales web portal
 Over 60 users from both head and dealer companies utilize the software, covering operations related to warranties, service contracts, dealing with 24h service requests and other post-sales business procedures.
- Design, development and support of Training web portal
 Over 30 users utilize the software, covering organisation of technical and non-technical training (announcements, signups and test results) for both company and external personnel. Used by Mercedes-Benz Hungary for the same purpose.

CONTRACT WORK, 1998 - present

WEB DEVELOPER

Projects requiring both back-end and front-end software development (mainly dynamic, database driven websites developed in PHP with MySQL as DBMS), support and maintenance.

Type of work undertaken in projects:

- Website design and web application development
- Search engine optimization, online marketing and promotions
- Customer technical support and web site maintenance